Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shashiram-reddy-piendla-2942b215 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Web Services
SQL
XML

Shashiram Reddy Piendla

Engineering Manager | .Net | SQL | Angular | AWS | Azure | DevOps | Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Summary

Engineering Manager with 16+ years of overall experience in handling various projects from start to end. Well-versed with transforming requirements to end product with industry-standard practices and technologies.

Well experienced in Exploratory Data Analysis, Data Cleaning, Statistical analysis and Predictive Modelling. Highly skilled in Python, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Computer Vision and NLP

Well experienced in delivering solutions developed in .Net, SQL, SSIS, Angular and AWS.

Worked on Call Center, Capital markets, Healthcare and e-Commerce domains.

Experience

Cognizant
Sr. Manager - Projects
April 2022 - Present (2 years 9 months)
Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Shore Infotech India Private Limited 12 years 8 months

Engineering Manager April 2019 - April 2022 (3 years 1 month) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Sr. Technical Lead February 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 2 months) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Technical Lead May 2013 - January 2018 (4 years 9 months) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Sr. Software Engineer September 2009 - April 2013 (3 years 8 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Patni Computer Systems Ltd Sr. Software Engineer December 2007 - August 2009 (1 year 9 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Education

Osmania University

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Software Engineering

Osmania University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Mathematics